Guide to the Leo Lerman papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Professional Files, 1922-1994
  - Subseries III.2: Writings, 1922-1994
    - New York Times Book Review
      - “The Gilded Age of Edith Wharton"-- review of An Edith Wharton Treasury, 1950 (Box 49)
      - “Sir Osbert’s Heartfelt Chronicle Dissolution"-- review of Sitwell’s Noble Essences, 1950 (Box 49)
      - “Scientist’s Dilemma"-- review of Nigel Balchin’s Who is my Neighbor? 1950 (Box 49)
      - “Some People and Places"-- review of Enid Bagnold’s The Loved and Envied, 1950 (Box 49)
      - “Widow Thorne and Her Son"-- review of Grace Zaring Stone’s The Grotto, 1951 (Box 49)
      - “I Just Walked on Stage"-- review of Garden and Biancolli’s Mary Garden’s Story, 1951 (Box 49)
      - “Glitter in Focus"-- review of Beaton’s Photobiography, 1951 (Box 49)
      - “Select and Edwardian"-- review of Leverson’s The Limit, 1951 (Box 49)
      - “Everybody Stops at the Shelbourne"-- review of Eileen Bigland’s Shelbourne Hotel, 1951 (Box 49)
      - “Everyone Read Her and No One Was Bored "-- review of Bowen’s Ouida, 1951 (Box 49)
      - “…And the Czar Walked on Tiptoe"-- review of Stoeckl’s Not All Vanity, 1952 (Box 49)
      - “Some Points on the Ballet "-- review of John Martin’s World Book of Ballet, 1952 (Box 49)
      - “We do it Differently "-- review of Amy Vanderbilt’s …Complete Book of Etiquette, 1952 (Box 49)
      - “Foible Tweaking Comedy "-- review of Powell’s Venusberg and Agents and Patients, 1952 (Box 52)
      - “The Bond Was Frayed "-- review of Thomas Hinde’s Mr. Nicholas, 1953 (Box 52)
      - “Of Mama, Aunt Getty, and the Long Ago "-- review of Raverat’s Period Piece, 1953 (Box 52)
      - “The 1st Gentleman of Europe"-- review of Leslie’s The Great Corinthian, 1953 (Box 52)
      - “A Plaque in Place "-- review of Lancaster’s All Done from Memory, 1953 (Box 52)
      - “Always in Love, Mostly with Herself "-- review of Misia Sert’s Misia and the Muses, 1953 (Box 52)
      - “Mr. Sitwell’s Excursions"-- review of Selected Works of Sacheverell Sitwell, 1954 (Box 52)
      - “100 Friends "-- review of Kenneth Tynan’s Persona Grata, 1954 (Box 52)
      - “Headliner in the Glitter Glamour"-- review of Schiaparelli’s Shocking Life, 1954 (Box 52)
      - “One Long Love Story "-- review of Crosland’s Colette, 1954 (Box 52)
      - “A Book of Brigabrac"-- review of John Hadfield's The Saturday Book, 1954 (Box 52)
      - “With Uncatty Innocence"-- review of Sandy Wilson’s This Is Sylvia…, 1955 (Box 52)
      - “Glamour in the Millions"-- review of Herndon’s Bergdorf's on the Plaza, 1956 (Box 52)
      - “Ballet Bandwagon "-- review of Deakin’s At the Ballet and Krokover's New Borzoi Book of Ballets, 1956 (Box 52)
      - “As if They had Forever "-- review of Warren’s Peacocks and Avarice, 1957 (Box 52)
      - “Dust-Sifting with Profit"-- review of Sitwell’s English Eccentrics, 1957 (Box 52)
      - “All I Wanted Was to Go Somewheres,” 1958 (Box 52)
      - “The Curate’s Own Wonderful World "-- review of Kilvert’s Diary, 1960 (Box 52)
      - “A Great Day for Singing"-- review of Maurice Disher’s Victorian Song, 1956 (Box 52)
      - “Gentleman Came for Tea "-- review of Pearl’s Girl with the Swansdown Seat, 1956 (Box 52)
      - “Glamour in the Millions,” 1956 (Box 52)
      - “Written by Candlelight, in Black Coal "-- review of Bodart’s The Blue Dog and Other Fables…, 1956 (Box 52)
      - “Snips, Snails, Puppydog’s Tails...” 1956 (Box 52)
      - “Diversity is the Key "-- review of People…Places…Things…Ideas, 1957 (Box 52)
      - “The Right People, Places, and Things "-- review of Cecil Beaton’s The Face of the World, 1957 (Box 52)
      - “The Passionate Victorian"-- review of Stirling’s The Fine and the Wicked, 1958 (Box 52)
      - “Real Magic "-- review of Books of E. Nesbit, 1960 (Box 52)
      - “Recent Letters to Editor,” 1960 (Box 52)
      - “Tattoos and Wicked Gypsies "-- review of Talese’s New York…, 1961 (Box 52)
      - “What Daisy Did"-- review of Theo Lang’s The Darling Daisy Affair, 1966 (Box 52)
      - “Such Fun "-- review of P. Jullian’s Edward and the Edwardians, 1967 (Box 52)
    - The New York Times
      - "Dance: June Walk," 1961 (Box 52)
      - "Eva le Gallienne- Up from 14th Street," 1968 (Box 52)
      - “Jean Rosenthal 1912-1969”-- Obituary, 1969 (Box 52)
      - “Allene T. Plant is Dead at 83”-- Obituary, 1986 (Box 52)
    - The New Yorker Article, 1984 (Box 61)
    - Paris Vogue
      - “Tommy Tune,” 1982 November (Box 52)
      - "Inside New York," 1982 (Box 52)
      - “The Man and The Egg: Franco Zeffirilli,” 1984 August (Box 52)
    - The Philharmonic Symphony Society of NY-- Program Notes, 1945, (2 Folders) (Box 52)
    - Philharmonia Pop Concert-- Liner Notes, 1961 (Box 52)
    - Playbill
      - “Christmas Is New York,” 1958 (Box 52)
      - “Graven Images,” 1960 (Box 52)
      - “Count Zero: A Personal Tribute,” 1970 (Box 52)
      - “Books on the Bolshoi Ballet,” 1959 (Box 52)
      - “Stop, Look, and Listen,” undated (Box 52)
      - “Looking and Listening” Column
        - Assorted, 1960s (Box 52)
        - "Tourel, The Greatest" (Box 52)
        - "Bruno Walter" (Box 52)
        - "Vanity Fair" (Box 52)
        - 'The Two Camps" (Box 52)
        - "The New Callas" (Box 52)
        - "Marlowe and Others" (Box 52)
        - "The Big Practical Dream, Bel Geddes," 1960 (Box 52)
        - “Mostly Looking,” 1961 (Box 52)
        - "Maestro Toscanini," 1961 (Box 52)
        - "A Gentle Sound," 1961 (Box 52)
        - "There Was This Girl," 1961 (Box 52)
        - "Two, Strongly Biographical," 1962 (Box 52)
      - "The Playbill Attic" Column, 1957 1962, (2 Folders) (Box 53)
      - "The Playbill Diarist" Column, 1957-1959, (21 Folders) (Box 53)
      - Published Playbill issues, 1957-1994 (Box 56)
    - The Ruth York Golden Series, “Ruth,” 1967 (Box 53)
    - The Publishers Weekly
      - "Used Book Shop," 1939 (Box 53)
      - "Biography for Young People" with Helen Hoke, 1941 (Box 53)
      - "The Problem Book," 1941 (Box 53)
    - The Retail Bookseller,-- “Spring Sales Peak,” May 1943 (Box 53)
    - Rigoletto, “A Rigoletto Scrapbook”-- Liner Notes, 1960 (Box 53)
    - The Saturday Review of Literature/The Saturday of Review
      - “An Industry Within an Industry,” 1941 (Box 53)
      - “The Christmas Round Up,” 1941 (Box 53)
      - “Apparitionist Adventures"--Review of Pratt and De Camp’s Land of Unreason, 1942 (Box 53)
      - “Shearing"--Review of Joseph Shearing’s The Spectral Bride, 1942 (Box 53)
      - “Bumps in the Night "--Review of De La Mare’s The Walk Again, 1942 (Box 53)
      - “Guide to Books for Young People,” 1942 (Box 53)
      - “Biographies and Ideas,” 1942 (Box 53)
      - “Career and Informational,” 1942 (Box 53)
      - “The Christmas Round-Up,” 1942 (Box 53)
      - “Books for Young Gardeners,” 1943 (Box 53)
      - “Mlle. Rouchaud’s Human Document"--Review of Rouchaud’s Time of Our Lives, 1946 (Box 53)
      - “Variations on a Current Theme"--Review of Kavan’s Asylum Piece, 1946 (Box 53)
      - “A Novel of Occupied Germany "--Review of Wesley Towner’s The Liberators, 1946 (Box 53)
      - “A Wonderchild for 72 Years --Review of Selected Writings of Gertrude Stein, 1946 (Box 53)
      - “Twenty Folk Tales from Russia "--Review of Papashvily’s Yes and No Stories, 1946 (Box 53)
      - “Chronicle of Romantic Optimism"--Review of Kesten’s Ferdinand and Isabella, 1946 (Box 53)
      - “Poor Little Rich Business Girl "--Review of Rice’s Mirror, Mirror, 1946 (Box 53)
      - “A Way of Life Immortalized"--Review of Moore’s The Fair Field, 1947 (Box 53)
      - “Reading For Democracy,” 1942 (Box 53)
      - “An Edifice Built on Despair "--Review of Winwar’s The Haunted Palace: A Life of Edgar Allan Poe 1959 (Box 53)
      - “Shifting Prisms in a Durrellscape" --Review of Durrell’s Mount Olive 1959 (Box 53)
      - “Guide to Young People’s Books on Music” (Box 53)
      - “Hell in a Toned Up Pub" --Review of Sanson’s The Cautious Heart undated (Box 53)
      - Scholastic-- “Wings,” Chapter from da Vinci Biography, 1941 (Box 53)
    - Swan Lake -- Liner notes (Box 53)
    - Tomorrow
      - "New Fiction in Review" Column, 1942-1945, (10 Folders) (Box 53)
      - “A Time for Reading: A Plea for Phantasy in Children’s Books,” 1942 November (Box 53)
      - “Tomorrow’s People,” 1945 June (Box 53)
    - Tosca, “The Lives and Times of Floria Tosca”-- Liner Notes, 1958 (Box 53)
    - Linda Di Chamounix-- Liner Notes (Box 53)
    - Trinidad: Paintings by Helen Turner-- Catalog Copy, 1948 (Box 53)
    - Vanity Fair
      - “Letter From the Editor,” 1983 September- 1984 March, (7 Folders) (Box 53)
    - Vogue
      - “Two Facet Careers-Writers Who Teach,” 1947 (Box 53)
      - “Before Bandwagons,” 1943 1948, (2 Folders) (Box 53)
      - “Renaissance Profiles: Five Women of the Italian Renaissance,” 1942 (Box 53)
      - “Taken by the Gypsies,” 1963 (Box 53)
      - “Books to Give Your Children,” 1942 (Box 53)
      - “Welcome Marlene,” 1944 (Box 53)
      - “Victorian Crime Unmasked"-- Review of Elizabeth Jenkins’ Dr. Gully’s Story, 1972 (Box 53)
      - “Woody the Great,” 1972 (Box 53)
      - “The Astonishing Bertolucci,” 1973 (Box 53)
      - “Broadway Gains: 3 Winners, More to Come-- Reviews of Sunshine Boys, 6 Rms Riv VV, Last of Mrs. Lincoln, 1973 (Box 53)
      - “The Prince of Broadway: Harold Prince,” 1973 (Box 53)
      - “A Little Night Music,” 1973 (Box 53)
      - “What Such A Gorgeous Kid Like ‘Suzy Says’…,” 1973 (Box 53)
      - “The Influentials: Pauline Kael, Barbara Rose, Clive Barnes,” 1973 (Box 53)
      - “The Channing Wonder: Carol Channing,” 1974 (Box 53)
      - “Marlene: Marlene Dietrich,” 1992 (Box 53)
      - “People are Talking About,” 1974 March (Box 53)
      - “The Winners,” 1974 (Box 53)
      - “Upfront: TV: ‘The Autobiography of Miss Jane Pittman’,” 1974 (Box 53)
      - “Peter and His Cybil,” 1974 (Box 53)
      - “People are Talking About,” 1974 July (Box 53)
      - “The Greatest Pianist in the World: Vladimir Horowitz,” 1974 (Box 53)
      - “The Decorator’s Decorator: Billy Baldwin,” 1974 (Box 53)
      - “People are Talking About…,” 1975 January. March, (2 Folders) (Box 53)
      - “Your Kitchen Way to Give a White House Dinner,” 1975 (Box 53)
      - “A Loving Attention to Guests,” 1975 (Box 53)
      - “People are Talking About…,” 1975 May (Box 53)
      - “Monty Python Exposed,” 1975 (Box 53)
      - “Theater: ‘Travesties ‘The Norman Conquest’,” 1976 (Box 53)
      - “People are Talking About…,” 1976 April, August, (2 Folders) (Box 53)
      - Review of “The Romantic Agony” by Mario Praz, 1977 (Box 54)
      - “The Entertaining Mrs. Lambert,” 1980, (3 Folders) (Box 54)
      - “Gritti Palace: Small, Elegant Miracle on the Grand Canal,” 1980 (Box 54)
      - "Eternal Allure"-- Profile of Diana Vreeland, 1980 (Box 54)
      - “We’re Going to Maxim’s: La Belle Epoch,” 1982 (Box 54)
      - “How Now Victoria,” 1984 (Box 54)
        (written for Vogue, but unpublished)
      - “Coming Home to Proust"-- Review of Marcel Proust Selected Letters 1880-1903, 1983 (Box 54)
      - “People are Talking About,” 1983 (Box 54)
      - “The Truth About Hollywood"-- Review of Gavin Lambert’s Running Time, 1983 (Box 54)
      - “Jerry’s Girls,” 1986 (Box 54)
      - “Acting as Salvation"-- Review of Simon Callow’s Being an Actor, 1986 (Box 54)
      - “Call it Friendship, Call it Love,” 1987 (Box 54)
        (published under the title "The Tiny Terror: A Capote Memory")
      - “Animal Magnetism"-- Review of The Small Creatures of Beatrix Potter, 1988 (Box 54)
      - "Dr. Gully’s Story" (Box 54)
      - Scrapbooks, 1973-1976 (Box 102)
      - Scrapbooks, 1978-1979 (Box 56)
      - Published Volumes with Lerman's Writings, 1980-1992 (Box 61)
    - Willard Gallery -- Text for Molla Moss catalogue, 1948 (Box 54)
    - Unpublished or Unidentified Articles
      - Book Reviews (Box 54)
      - “The Self-Education of Hoyningen-Huene,” (Box 54)
      - 1970 (Box 54)
      - “Another Year, Another Place” (Box 54)
      - “A Bouquet For Callo,” Carl van Vechten Profile (Box 54)
      - “The Big Met: Metropolitan Opera House,” 1967 (Box 54)
      - “The Girl Who Fell Down,” 19671 (Box 54)
      - “A Life and a Death: Eleanora Mendelssohn" (Box 54)
      - “A Little Album for Tania” (Box 54)
        (Memorial for Isak Dinesen)
      - "The Shouting’s About-Parties!” or “Conversation on (Box 54)
      - Party Giving” (Box 54)
      - “Real People: Book Characters” outline, 1948 (Box 54)
      - Yul Brynner (Box 54)
      - "Amy Vanderbilt’s Complete Book of Etiquette" (Box 54)
      - “Manhattan: Blessed City” (Box 54)
      - “Sidney Janis” (Box 54)
      - “A Room of Their Own: Pages from a Constant Rereader’s Journal” (Box 54)
      - "The Most Happy Show in Town"-- Review of My Fair Lady, 1956 (Box 54)
      - “The World of the Fashion Magazine” (Box 54)
        (outline for a documentary)
      - “Italian Front by the Renaissance Masters” (Box 54)
      - “To See a Sound” (Box 54)
      - “Two Peaks a Year” (Box 54)
      - “Transatlantic Arts” (Box 54)
      - “Calvin Coolidge” (Box 54)
      - Review of Jan Potocki’s The Saragossa Manuscript… (Box 54)
      - “Curiouser and Curiouser” (Box 54)
      - ”Man of His Moment"-- Review of Adams’ Stendhal: Notes on a Novelist (Box 54)
      - "Graham Greene" (Box 54)
      - “Reading For You and Your Child” (Box 54)
      - “You’ll Never Be Asked Again!,” as Rachel Dudley (Box 54)
      - Research/Gossip, 1970 (Box 54)
      - Outline of Series of Talks to be Given at Metropolitan Museum (Box 54)
      - Quotations – Saved by Lerman (Box 54)
      - Christmas Wishlist, 1955 (Box 54)
    - Manuscripts Authored by Others
      - Ardoin, John-- Callas at Julliard, 1987 (Box 57)
      - Botto. Louis (Box 57)
      - Comden, Betty (Box 57)
      - Gordon, Ruth-- My Side, (4 Folders) (Box 57)
      - Gray, Francine du Plessix-- Rage and Fire (Box 57)
      - Hubert, Karen, 1922 (Box 58)
      - Loos, Mary Anita-- Maiden Voyage (Box 58)
      - Nappelbaum, Moses, 1984 (Box 58)
      - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy-- In the Russian Style (Box 58)
      - Shapiro, Jeffrey, 1984 (Box 58)
      - Trilling, Lionel-- The Beginning of the Journey, 1993 (Box 58)
      - Vreeland, Diana (Box 58)
      - Scripts and Screenplays-- Various (Box 59)
  - Subseries III.3: Research and Book Projects, 1969-1993
    This subseries includes research notes and drafts for Lerman's book projects, both realized and unrealized. A large portion of this subseries is devoted to his history of the Metropolitan Museum of Art, The Museum: One Hundred Years and the Metropolitan Museum of Art, a volume commissioned by the museum to celebrate its centennial.
    - The Museum
      - Centennial (Box 62)
      - Centennial Ball, 1970 (Box 62)
      - Layout Lists (Box 62)
      - Notes (Box 62)
      - Publicity and Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 62)
      - Publicity and Congratulations, 1969, (2 Folders) (Box 62)
      - Photographs (Box 62)
      - Manuscript
        - Complete (Box 62)
        - Prefatory Material (Box 62)
        - Chapter I-- "All for Art", (2 Folders) (Box 62)
        - 1880-1890 (Box 62)
        - 1890-1899 (Box 62)
        - 1900-1901 (Box 62)
        - 1910-1919 (Box 62)
        - 1920-1929 (Box 62)
        - 1930-1939 (Box 62)
        - 1940-1970 (Box 62)
        - 1940-1949 (Box 62)
        - 1950-1959 (Box 62)
        - 1960-1969 (Box 62)
      - Research Notes (oversized) (Box 68)
        - General, (2 Folders) (Box 68)
        - 1866-1889 (Box 68)
        - 1890-1899 (Box 68)
        - 1900-1909 (Box 68)
        - 1910-1919 (Box 68)
        - 1920-1929 (Box 68)
        - 1930-1939 (Box 68)
        - 1940-1970 (Box 68)
        - 1970 and After (Box 68)
      - Research Notes (Box 63)
        - Final Notes (Box 63)
        - Timeline (Box 63)
        - Chronologies (Box 63)
        - 1920s (Box 63)
        - 1940s (Box 63)
        - 1950s, (7 Folders) (Box 63)
        - 1960s, (10 Folders) (Box 63)
        - End of Book (Box 63)
        - Collecting Range (Box 63)
        - Departments (Box 63)
      - Research Files
        - General, (3 Folders) (Box 63)
        - General, (9 Folders) (Box 64)
        - 1900 (Box 64)
        - 1968 (Box 64)
        - Benjamin Altman (Box 64)
        - The American Museum of Natural History (Box 64)
        - The American Wing (Box 64)
        - Art Deco (Box 64)
        - Central Park (Box 64)
        - Chess (Box 64)
        - The Cloisters (Box 64)
        - The Costume Institute, (2 Folders) (Box 64)
        - Forgery (Box 65)
        - "Harlem on My Mind" Exhibition (Box 65)
        - Thomas Hoving (Box 65)
        - Hudson River School (Box 65)
        - Lists (Box 65)
        - Manet (Box 65)
        - Museums in the United States (Box 65)
      - Research-- Note Cards (Box 65)
    - Research-- Note Cards (Box 66-67)
    - Research Files for Unrealized Books
      - Sotheby's History (Box 69-70)
      - Theatre History (Box 71)
      - Opera (Box 71)
      - The Victorian Reader (Box 71)
      - The D'Este Sisters (Box 72)
      - Call It Friendship, Call it Love-- Autobiography-- Notes and Manuscript Drafts, 1990-1993 (Box 73-74)
- Series IV: Personal Files, 1936-1994
  This series is comprised of Lerman's personal files, including juvenalia, personal documents, journals, and datebooks. Also included are a small number of books that had personal significance to Lerman.
  - Subseries IV.1: General Personal Files, 1936-1994
    This subseries includes files and documents relating to Lerman's personal life, including some of his school assignments, as well as early writings and personal documents such as passports. The subseries also includes material about to his various homes, and documentation relating to his finances and end-of-life decisions.
    - Juvenalia
      - General (Box 76)
      - Writings, (2 Folders) (Box 76)
      - Poetry and Sketches (Box 76)
      - Newtown High School, (4 Folders) (Box 76)
      - Poetry, 1936-1938 (Box 76)
    - Personal-- General (Box 76)
    - Personal Documents (Box 76)
      (Birth Certificate, Passports, etc.)
    - Social Security (Box 76)
    - Recipes (Box 76)
    - Will (Box 76)
    - Financial Documents
      - General, 1988-1994 (Box 76)
      - Account Books, 1943-1986 (Box 77)
      - Book Receipts, 1951-1952 (Box 76)
      - Donations, 1940-1993 (Box 76)
      - Lerman International Studies Award, 1992-1994, (5 Folders) (Box 76)
      - Yale Scholarship (Box 76)
    - Residences
      - Gramercy Park Hotel, 1986 (Box 76)
      - East End Avenue (Box 76)
      - East 88th Street (Box 76)
      - 1453 Lexington (Box 76)
      - 205 W. 57th Street-- The Osborne (Box 76)
      - Chelsea Mini Storage (Box 76)
    - Photographs of Lerman (Box 76)
      (mostly published photographs-- the bulk of photographs can be found in Series V: Photographs)
    - Drawings and Paintings of Lerman (Box 76)
    - Memorabilia (Box 76)
    - Lerman Memorial Tribute, 1994, (2 Folders) (Box 76)
    - Social Events and Parties
      - Invitations to Events Hosted by Others, (4 Folders) (Box 78)
      - Invitation Lists and Menus for Parties Thrown by Lerman, 1940-1994, (87 Folders) (Box 78)
  - Subseries IV.2: Journals, 1940-1994
    Lerman's journals comprise the bulk of the series. The journals, generally small notebooks, consist of diary entries and research notes for ongoing projects, as well as clippings, memorabilia and other inserted material. Most of the journals include notes penciled in by Stephen Pascal that provide explication of Lerman's abbreviations and personal short hand notations, as well as, on occasion, contextual information about the events described in the journals.
    - Miscellaneous Items found with Journals (Box 79)
    - 1940-1950 August (Box 79)
    - 1951 January-1955 March (Box 80)
    - 1955 May- 1965 February (Box 81)
    - 1965 February- 1971 May (Box 82)
    - 1971 May- 1973 June (Box 83)
    - 1973 June- 1978 February (Box 84)
    - 1978 May- 1983 January (Box 85)
    - 1983 January- 1987 June (Box 86)
    - 1987 May- 1992 August (Box 87)
  - Subseries IV.3 Address and Date Books, 1943-1994
    This subseries includes Lerman's Datebooks and Address Books. His datebooks give detailed information about his appointments, both business and personal throughout his career.
    - Address Books (Box 88)
    - Date Books
      - 1943-1963 (Box 89)
      - 1965-1984 (Box 90)
      - 1985-1994 (Box 91)
    - Books (Box 92)
- Series V: Photographs, 1893-1994
  The photographs series includes photographs of Lerman and his friends, family, and professional contacts-- both formal portraits and candid snapshots. Many of the photographs filed as "Work and Professional" include images that accompanied articles written or edited by Lerman for publication in magazines. The "Personalities" file is comprised, primarily, of formal headshots, often signed, collected by Lerman.
  - Early Life, 1914-1935 (Box 93)
  - Theatre Career, 1934-1954 (Box 93)
  - Family, 1893-1973 (Box 93)
  - Individual Shots, 1937-1993, (7 Folders) (Box 93)
  - Work and Professional, 1945-1994, (8 Folders) (Box 94)
  - Work and Professional-- Friends of George Spelvin Events, 1971-1981, (6 Folders) (Box 94)
  - Lerman-- With Famous Personalities, 1939-1993, (4 Folders) (Box 95)
  - Famous Personalities, 1914-1991, (4 Folders) (Box 95)
  - Friends, (5 Folders) (Box 96)
  - Gray Foy (Box 96)
  - Richard Hunter and Howard Rothschild, (3 Folders) (Box 96)
  - Travel, 1937-1979, (5 Folders) (Box 97)
  - Photos Taken by Arnold Weissberger, (4 Folders) (Box 97)
  - Oversized Photographs (Box 98-99)
  - Slides (Box 100)